Guide to the Jim Kobs papers, 1954-2015 and undated RL.11721
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jim Kobs papers
1954-2015 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kobs, Jim
RL.11721
40.0 Linear Feet
Direct marketing and advertising executive based primarily in Chicago, Ill. Jim Kobs papers include: correspondence, mail order catalogs, mailings, print advertisements and advertising designs, research reports, slides and photographs and audiovisual materials (audiocassettes, videocassettes, 16mm film, DVD) that document Kobs' career in direct, database and catalog marketing. Companies and institutions represented include: Amoco, AT&T, Bankers Life, Boys and Girls Clubs of Chicago, DHL, Direct Mail Advertising Association (DMAA), Direct Mail Marketing Association (DMMA), Direct Marketing Association (DMA), Encyclopedia Britannica, Gander Mountain, General Electric, General Mills, Hewlett-Packard, Honeywell, Mayo Clinic, Montgomery Ward, Playboy, Prudential, Scott Paper, Tupperware, U.S. Navy recruiting, Wayside Gardens and Xerox. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Early Career; Stone & Adler; Kobs & Brady; Kobs Gregory Passavant; Writings and Speeches; Audiovisual Materials
Biographical / Historical
Direct marketing and advertising executive based primarily in Chicago, Ill. Born Chicago, 1938; BA Journalism, University of Illinois, Champaign-Urbana, 1960; Polk Brothers/Jack Petterson and Associates, 1957-1958; Rylander Company, 1960-1962; Combined Registry Company, 1961-1965; American Peoples Press, 1965-1967; James F. Kobs/Advertising, 1966-on; Stone & Adler, 1967-1977; Bankers Life and Casualty, 1977; Kobs & Brady, 1978-1988; Kobs Gregory Passavant, 1989-2002; Kobs Strategic Consulting, 1989-on
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Jim Kobs papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2014 and 2018.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Archie R. Slabaugh collection of direct mail literature
Bates Worldwide records
Henry W. Jones papers
John Stevenson papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Burt Manning papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic advertisements
J. Walter Thompson Company. John R. Mayer papers
Lester Wunderman papers
Wunderman archives
Collection Overview
Jim Kobs papers include: correspondence, mail order catalogs, mailings, print advertisements and advertising designs, research reports, slides and photographs and audiovisual materials (audiocassettes, videocassettes, 16mm film, DVD) that document Kobs' career in direct, database and catalog marketing. Companies and institutions represented include: Amoco, AT&T, Bankers Life, Boys and Girls Clubs of Chicago, DHL, Direct Mail Advertising Association (DMAA), Direct Mail Marketing Association (DMMA), Direct Marketing Association (DMA), Encyclopedia Britannica, Gander Mountain, General Electric, General Mills, Hewlett-Packard, Honeywell, Mayo Clinic, Montgomery Ward, Playboy, Prudential, Scott Paper, Tupperware, U.S. Navy recruiting, Wayside Gardens and Xerox. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- Illinois -- Chicago; Advertising executives -- United States; Direct marketing; Advertising, Direct-mail -- History; Advertising -- Databases; Marketing -- United States -- History -- Databases; Mail order catalogs; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Kobs and Draft (Firm); Amoco Oil Company; General Electric Company; General Mills, Inc; Honeywell Inc; Prudential Insurance Company of America; Xerox Corporation; United States. Navy -- Recruiting, enlistment, etc.; AT&T (Firm); Mayo Clinic
- General Files, 1966-2003 and undated; 1
  - Beyond the Basics seminar slides, undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - CADM (Chicago Association of Direct Marketing)--A Response Orientation, 1980 (Box 1)
  - CADM--Beyond the Basics, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Direct Marketing Magazine--Echo Awards issues, 1966-1997 (Box 36)
  - DMA (Direct Marketing Association)--Conference Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - DMA--Consumer Acceptance Task Force, 1987 (Box 1)
  - DMAA (Direct Mail Advertising Association)--Councils, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
  - DMAA--New York Times, 1968-1973 (Box 1)
  - DMAA--Publicity, advertising, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes issues of PR Hotline newsletter
  - DMMA (Direct Mail/Marketing Association)--Awards, 1974 (Box 1)
    Includes award materials for Hewlett-Packard mailing
  - DMMA--Education Foundation curricula, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - DMMA--Marketing Council, 1975-1978 (Box 1)
  - DMMA--TRAC Day, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Jim Kobs Hall of Fame outline, undated (Box 1)
  - Hoke Communications/DMA, 1986 (Box 1)
    Issues involving Hoke management of Direct Marketing Magazine subscriptions and distribution
  - Northwestern University, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Northwestern University--Graduate course, 1998; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Northwestern University--Undergraduate course, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Publicity --Personal, 1979-1996 (Box 1)
  - Teaching aids with Bonnie DeLay (DMA), 1985 (Box 1)
  - University of Chicago--Strategic Direct Marketing course--Binder 1, 2003 (Box 1)
  - University of Chicago--Strategic Direct Marketing course--Binder 2, 2003; 5 folders (Box 1)
- Early Career, 1954-1968 and undated; 2
  - American Peoples Press, 1965-1968 and undated; 1
    - Acknowledgement letters, undated (Box 2)
    - Advertising reports, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
    - Allenite Home Workshop, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
    - Armac pool table, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Bell & Howell Home Movie Outfit, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Columbia Lively Years, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Companion Library test mailing, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Free rides, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Fulls mailed, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Gardening Encylopedia, 1967 (Box 2)
    - International Silver tableware test mailing, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Lennox dinnerware, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Load-up letters, undated (Box 2)
    - Magnus Chord Organ, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Mailing checklist, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Modern Home Sewing Machine, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Multi-mailer, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
    - Neevel luggage set, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Recliner chair, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Results, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
    - Royal typewriter, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
    - Saunda facial sauna, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
    - Science Encyclopedia supplement, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Shetland Versa-Mixer, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Test mailings, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Tufram Teflon cookware, 1966 (Box 2)
    - USA Lands and Its People, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
    - Webster XL-500 typewriter, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Yearbook, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Young People's Book Club, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Young People's Story of Our Heritage, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Combined Registry, 1962-1966 and undated; 2
    - Book and record mailings, approximately 1963-1965 (Box 2)
    - Progress, 1963-1966 (Box 2)
    - Science of Success course, undated (Box 2)
    - Space (print) ads, 1963-1965 (Box 2)
    - Success Unlimited, 1962-1965 (Box 2)
  - Jack Petterson and Associates, 1958; 3
    - Advertising samples, 1958; 2 folders (Box OV1)
  - James F. Kobs/Advertising, 1965-1971; 4
    - Combined Insurance Company of America, 1965-1971 (Box 2)
      Dividend policy program recommendations and mailings
  - Polk Brothers, 1954-1958; 5
    - Advertising samples, 1954-1958 (Box 2)
    - Advertising samples, 1954-1958 (Box OV1)
  - Rylander, 1960-1962; 6
    - National Advertising Company--Mailer announcing Heath Ice Cream Bars, approximately 1960 (Box 26)
    - Samples, 1960-1962 (Box 2)
    - Samples--Binder 1, A-L, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
      Includes: Airguide Instrument; American Dental Association; Robert Bartlett Realty; Down Beat; Harris Trust and Savings Bank
    - Samples--Binder 2, M-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
      Includes: Motorola; 3M; Mountain Valley Mineral Water; National Association of Furniture Manufacturers; Old Ben Coal; Pure Oil; Seagrams
- Stone & Adler, 1961-1979 and undated; 3
  - Administrative and General Files, 1961-1978 and undated; 7
    - 10 Steps to That Golden Idea, 1977 (Box 4)
    - 99 Proven Direct Response Offers (Jim Kobs), 1975 (Box 4)
    - Advertising Age Direct Mail/Mail Order Clip File, 1967 (Box 4)
      File of Bob Stone articles
    - Agreements and contracts, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
      Contracts with Hallmark, Illinois Bell, Old American Insurance, Olen, Six Flags, Statistical Tabulating, U.S. News & World Report
    - Book chapter, 1961-1973 (Box 4)
      Correspondence, drafts, related material for "Creating Direct Mail" project; includes copy of Robert Stone, "How to Write Direct Mail Copy that Sells"
    - Dartnell booklet, 1974 (Box 4)
      "24 Ways to Improve Your Direct Mail Results" written by Jim Kobs; includes booklet, manuscripts, related materials
    - Direct Marketing Report (newsletter)--Binder 1, 1967-1971; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Direct Marketing Report (newsletter)--Binder 2, 1971-1977; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Employee handbook, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Forms, undated (Box 4)
    - House ads, 1967-1977 (Box 4)
    - How An All-American Boy Sold VIP's on the College Market (Jim Kobs), 1970 (Box 4)
    - In Pursuit of Excellence (Bob Stone), 1978 (Box 4)
    - Insider News (S&A newsletter), 1977-1978 (Box 4)
    - Inter-Office Seminar, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Memos and miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Postal and legal issues, 1967-1978; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Promotion and publicity, 1971-1978; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - You Learn the Most Amazing Things by Testing (Jim Kobs), undated (Box 4)
  - Clients, 1967-1979; 8
    - A.B. Dick, 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Airline Passengers Association (APA), 1968-1971; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Alan Drey Company, 1967-1970 (Box 4)
    - Ambassador Leather Goods, 1972-1975; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Amsterdam Printing, 1967-1970; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Career Academy--Marketing Program (binder), 1970 (Box 5)
    - Career Academy--Marketing Program (binder), 1970 (Box OV1)
    - Crain Books, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
    - Dartnell Subscription Services, 1969-1974 (Box 5)
    - Dartnell Subscription Services--Marketing Program (binder), 1971 (Box 5)
    - Dartnell Subscription Services, 1969-1974 (Box OV1)
      Includes promotion with Arnold Palmer
    - Direct Mail Advertising Association, 1978 (Box OV1)
    - Direct Mail/Marketing Association, 1973 (Box OV1)
    - Dow Theory Forecasts, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica--New Business Presentation, 1975 (Box 5)
      Cases and examples of other S&A work
    - Encyclopedia Britannica--New Business Presentation, 1977 (Box OV1)
    - Fidelity File Box--Marketing Program (binder), 1971 (Box 5)
    - Fidelity Products, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - Haband, 1970 (Box OV1)
    - Hallmark, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
    - Hallmark, 1977-1978 (Box OV1)
    - Hallmark--Grandparents Club, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Hallmark--Hallmark Collection, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Hallmark--Little Gallery, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Heath Schlumberger (Heath Kits), 1973-1975; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Heath Schlumberger (Heath Kits), 1973-1975 (Box OV1)
    - Hewlett-Packard, Advanced Products Division, 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Hewlett-Packard, Advanced Products Division, 1974-1979 (Box OV1)
    - Illinois Bell, 1977-1978; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Lanier Business Products, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
    - Lanier Business Products, 1974 (Box OV1)
    - LaSalle Extension University, 1970-1972; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Lehigh Acres--Marketing Plan (binder), 1977 (Box 6)
    - MDC (Market Development Corporation), 1967-1969 (Box 6)
    - MDC (Market Development Corporation), 1968 (Box OV1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1974 (Box 6)
      Includes: Hal Leonard, Diners Club
    - NBL (National Business Lists), 1971 (Box 6)
    - Old American Insurance, 1972-1976 (Box 6)
    - Old American Insurance--Marketing Program (binder), 1974 (Box 6)
    - Old American Insurance--Marketing Program (binder), 1973-1975 (Box OV1)
    - Packard (J. Packard Custom Shirtmakers), 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Six Flags, 1977-1978; 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Skeptic Magazine, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
    - Sunset House, 1971-1973; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Sunset House, 1971-1973 (Box OV1)
    - Tru-Photo (Rapid Photo), 1967 (Box 6)
    - U.S. News & World Report, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - United Republican Fund of Illinois, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Wayside Gardens, 1968-1971 (Box 6)
    - Wayside Gardens--Sales Analysis and Planning Program (binder), 1969 (Box 6)
    - Wayside Gardens--Sales Analysis and Planning Program (binder), 1969-1970 (Box OV1)
  - Sample Creative Binders, 1967-1978; 9
    - Airline Passengers Association (APA), 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Alan Drey Company, 1968-1969; 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Ambassador Leather Goods, 1972-1974 (Box 6)
    - Amsterdam Printing, 1967-1970; 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Career Academy, 1970; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Dartnell, 1970-1971; 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Direct Mail/Marketing Association, 1971-1973 (Box 7)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
    - Fidelity Products/Fidelity File Box, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Hallmark, 1976-1978 (Box 7)
    - Heath Schlumberger (Heath Kits), 1974 (Box 7)
    - Hewlett-Packard, binder 1, 1972-1973; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Hewlett-Packard, binder 2, 1974-1975; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Illinois Bell, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
    - Lanier Business Products, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
    - LaSalle Extension University, 1974 (Box 8)
    - MDC (Market Development Corporation), 1967-1969 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1971; 3 folders (Box 8)
      Includes: J. Packard, AB Dick, National Deer Hunters Association, United Republican Fund of Illinois
    - NBL (National Business Lists), 1971 (Box 8)
    - Old American Insurance--Mailings, 1975-1978; 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Old American Insurance--Space ads and television, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
    - Six Flags, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
    - Stat:Tab (Statistical Tabulating Corporation), 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Sunset House, 1971-1973 (Box 8)
    - Sunset House--Catalogs, 1971-1973; 4 folders (Box 8)
    - Truman Library, 1974-1976; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Wayside Gardens, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
- Kobs & Brady, 1977-1989; 4
  - Administrative and General Files, 1977-1988; 10
    - Account management reports, 1981-1988; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Annual billings, 1979-1988 (Box 9)
    - Awards, 1979-1986 (Box 9)
    - Client evaluations, 1982-1987 (Box 9)
    - Downs Award, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Fee increases, 1980-1987 (Box 9)
    - Forms, 1983-1987 (Box 9)
    - House ads, 1980-1987 (Box 9)
    - International, 1981-1988; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Job descriptions, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Minneapolis Office, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
      K&B acquired Campbell-Mithun's direct marketing operations in Minneapolis
    - New business credentials script, 1984-1987 (Box 9)
    - New business strategy, 1986-1988 (Box 9)
    - New York Office, 1982-1987 (Box 9)
    - Planning, 1979-1987; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Promotion and publicity, 1978-1987; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - ROP (Review of Performance) System, 1977-1987 (Box 9)
    - Saatchi takeover, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Strategic planning, 1984-1987 (Box 9)
    - Supervisor seminar, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Systems and Procedures Manual, 1983; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Ted Bates acquisition, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Television reel script, 1985-1987 (Box 9)
    - Training programs, 1986-1988 (Box 9)
    - West coast office (San Francisco), 1986-1988 (Box 9)
  - Clients, 1977-1989; 11
    - 3M, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
    - 800 Spirits, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Ace Pecan, 1984-1986 (Box 9)
    - Advertising Age, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - Allstate, 1985-1987; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Allstate--Universal Life Marketing Plan, 1985 (Box 10)
    - American Bar Association, 1984 (Box 10)
    - American Express Life Insurance, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
    - American Home Shield, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
    - Ameritech, 1984-1987 (Box 10)
    - Amoco, 1983-1988; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Anheuser-Busch, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
    - AT&T, 1981-1984 (Box 10)
    - Avis, 1985-1987 (Box 10)
    - Bank of America, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Bankers Life & Casualty, 1979-1988; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Bankers Life & Casualty--Direct Marketing Organization and Operation (binder), 1981 (Box 10)
    - Bankers Life & Casualty--Media Recommendation (binder), 1978 (Box 10)
    - Bell South, 1984-1986 (Box 10)
    - Bell System, 1978-1982; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Bell System--Test Summaries (binder), 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - Beltone, 1984-1986 (Box 10)
    - Brown & Williamson, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
    - Brown & Williamson--Direct Marketing: The Alternative `Tool (binder), 1983 (Box 10)
    - CBS Video, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati Bell, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati Microwave, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
    - Colgate-Palmolive, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
    - Commodore, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Continental Cablevision/Cellular One, 1985-1987 (Box 10)
    - Crain Books, 1984-1988 (Box 10)
    - Dartnell, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
    - Deluxe Computer Forms, 1984-1988 (Box 10)
    - DHL, 1983-1988; 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Diners Club, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Direct Marketing Association--Shopping at Home booklet, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Eddie Bauer, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Electrolux, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1978-1980 (Box 11)
    - Fidelity Investments, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - First Chicago/Visa, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Foster Parents Plan, 1983-1987; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Frederick's of Hollywood, 1985-1989 (Box 11)
    - Fujitsu Systems, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Garon Products, 1988 (Box 11)
    - General Electric, 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - General Electric--Business Plan (binder), approximately 1982 (Box 11)
    - General Mills/Betty Crocker, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Genesco, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Gillette, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Grolier Book Club, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Group W Cable of Chicago, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
    - Happy Trails Resorts, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Harrah's Marina Hotel Casino, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Hartmarx, 1986 (Box 11)
    - HBO, 1984-1988 (Box 11)
    - Helene Curtis, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Highland Fraser Firs, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Honeywell Protection Services, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Honeywell Protection Services--Marketing Plan (binder), 1981 (Box 11)
    - Hyatt, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Informatics General, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Kal Kan, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - Keron Products, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Kroger, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
    - Life Fitness, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - Littleton Stamp & Coin, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Mayo Clinic, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Mayo Clinic--Presentation (binder), 1982 (Box 12)
    - Medialink, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Merabank, 1986-1988 (Box 12)
    - Meridan, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Metromail, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Miles Homes, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Montgomery Wards, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - Myron Manufacturing, 1984 (Box 12)
    - National Cable Month (Richebourg Marketing), 1987 (Box 12)
    - NBC Enterprises, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Nestle, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
    - New England Business Service (NEBS), 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - New England Business Service (NEBS)--Marketing Plan (binder), 1981 (Box 12)
    - Nissan, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
    - No Nonsense Fashions, 1982 (Box 12)
    - No Nonsense Fashions--Direct Marketing Business Plan (binder), 1982 (Box 12)
    - North American Philips, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - Noxell, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Pacific Northwest Bell, 1981-1988 (Box 12)
    - Paramount Pictures, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
    - Paramount Pictures--Merchandising Program Revised Strategic Overview (binder), 1987 (Box 12)
    - Peace Corps/Ad Council, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Pepsi-Cola Company, 1985-1986 (Box 12)
    - Pizza Hut (home delivery), 1985-1986 (Box 12)
    - Pizza Hut Delivery (binder), 1985 (Box 12)
    - Playboy, 1984-1987; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Playboy--Best of the Playboy Channel Test Plan (binder), 1987 (Box 12)
    - Playboy--Playboy Home Videos Business Plan (binder), 1987; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Polaroid, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
    - Prentice-Hall, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Prince Matchabelli, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - Procter & Gamble, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - Prudential, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Quill, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Quill--Customer Acquisition Recommendation (binder), 1986 (Box 12)
    - Randy Hundley Baseball Camps, 1984-1987 (Box 13)
    - Rusty Jones, 1984-1987 (Box 13)
    - Scientific Computers, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Scott Paper, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Scott Paper--Business Plans (binder), 1982; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Seagrams, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - Shaklee, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
    - Share Development, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - Shopsmith, 1979-1985 (Box 13)
    - Signature Group, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
      Tie-in with Montgomery Ward, Montgomery Ward Auto Club
    - Sotheby's, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Southern Bell, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - Sperry, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - Sports Network, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Stouffer Foods--Business Plan (binder), 1978 (Box 13)
    - Times Mirror--Books, 1985-1987 (Box 13)
    - Times Mirror--Cable, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
    - Tupperware, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - U.S. Mint, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
    - U.S. Navy Recruiting Command, 1984-1987 (Box 13)
    - Vermont American (Tools, Etc.), 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - Viacom, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Viewtron/Viewdata, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - Western Electric--Results Analysis Com Key 416 System (binder), 1980 (Box 13)
    - Western Publishing, 1981-1988 (Box 13)
    - Wilton Enterprises, 1981-1984 (Box 13)
    - Xerox, 1981-1984 (Box 13)
    - Xerox--Catalog, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Xerox--Copier sales, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Xerox--Diener, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
    - Xerox--Xerox 500 Business Plan (binder), 1979 (Box 13)
  - Sample Mailings, 1978-1988; 12
    - Binder 1, 1978 (Box 13)
      Includes: Bankers Life and Casualty
    - Binder 2, 1979; 2 folders (Box 13)
      Includes: American Medical Association, Bankers Life and Casualty, Demco, LaSalle Extension University, Source EDP
    - Binder 3, 1980 (Box 13)
      Includes: Bankers Life and Casualty, Demco, LaSalle Extension University
    - Binder 4, 1981; 5 folders (Box 14)
      Includes: Bankers Life and Casualty, Computer Sciences, Crain Books, Demco, Emerald Tree, General Electric, Littleton Coin and Stamp, Montgomery Ward, 3M, TRW-Fujitsu, Shopsmith, Wilton, New England Business Service (NEBS)
    - Binder 5, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
      Includes: Deluxe Computer Forms, Demco, Encyclopedia Britannica, Helene Curtis, Nestle, Newsweek, Premex
    - Binder 6, 1984; 6 folders (Box 14)
      Includes: Ace Pecan, Amoco, Bankers Life and Casualty, Deluxe, DHL, Foster Parents, General Mills, Gillette, Helene Curtis, Informatics, Mayo Clinic, Miles Homes, Myron, Nestle, Providence St. Mel, Share Senior Care, Wards
    - Binder 7, 1985; 4 folders (Box 14)
      Includes: Ace Pecan, Allstate, Avis, Beltone, Control Data, Deluxe, DHL, Foster Parents, General Electric, General Mills, Group W Cable, Happy Trails, Honeywell, Prince Matchabelli, Randy Hundley Baseball, Prudential, Quill, Viewtron, Sperry
    - Binder 8, 1986; 4 folders (Box 14)
      Includes: Allstate, Ameritech Mobile, Anheuser-Busch, Avis, Bally Fitness, Bankers Life and Casualty, Deluxe, Diners Club, Foster Parents, Group W Cable, HBO, Pizza Hut, Randy Hundley Baseball, Kroger, Viewtron, Sperry
    - Binder 9, 1987; 5 folders (Box 15)